U.S. Emergency Board No. 179 Exhibits and Related Material 5030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Emergency Board No. 179 Exhibits and Related Material
1960-1971
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Emergency Board
Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America (BRSA)
5030
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Exhibits and related material of the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen's case before the President's Emergency Board No. 179.
3113325
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 21, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5006: U.S. Emergency Board No. 174 Records 5007: U.S. Emergency Board No. 175 Transcripts and Exhibits 5012: Saul Wallen Papers 5027: U.S. Emergency Board No. 178 Transcripts 5030 MB: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America Memorabilia 5036: U.S. Emergency Boards under the Railway Labor Act Reports 5037: U.S. Emergency Board No. 81 Records 5038: U.S. Emergency Board No. 94 Records 5039: U.S. Emergency Board No. 98 Records 5040: U.S. Emergency Board No. 106 Records 5042: U.S. Emergency Board No. 111 Records 5043: U.S. Emergency Board No. 114 Records 5044: U.S. Emergency Board No. 116 Reports and Exhibits 5045: U.S. Emergency Board No. 118 Records 5046: U.S. Emergency Board No. 119 Records 5047: U.S. Emergency Board No. 120 Records 5048: U.S. Emergency Board No. 121 Records 5050: U.S. Emergency Board No. 124 Records 5051: U.S. Emergency Board No. 125 Records 5052: U.S. Emergency Board No. 129 Records 5053: U.S. Emergency Board No. 130 Records 5054: U.S. Emergency Board No. 133 Exhibits 5055: U.S. Emergency Board No. 134 Records 5056: U.S. Emergency Board No. 135 Records 5057: U.S. Emergency Board No. 137 Transcript of Proceedings and Exhibits 5058: U.S. Emergency Board No. 138 Records 5059: U.S. Emergency Board No. 142 Records 5060: U.S. Emergency Board No. 145 Records 5061: U.S. Emergency Board No. 146 Records 5062: U.S. Emergency Board No. 154 Records 5064: U.S. Emergency Board No. 169 Transcript of Proceedings and Exhibits 5075: U.S. Emergency Board under the Taft Hartley Act Records 5579: National Mediation Board Emergency Board 180, Train Crew Consists 5934: Arthur Stark Papers on the President's Emergency Board #219
Collective bargaining -- Railroads -- United States; United States. Emergency Board No. 179.; Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America
3113325
- Emergency Board 179 Transcript Pages 1-149, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 1)
- Emergency Board 179 Transcript Pages 150-282, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 2)
- Emergency Board 179 Transcript Pages 283-392, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 3)
- Emergency Board 179 Transcript Pages 393-560, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 4)
- Emergency Board 179 Transcript Pages 561-729, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 5)
- Emergency Board 179 Transcript Pages 730-885, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 6)
- Closing Brief for the Carriers, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 7)
- Carriers' Exhibits No. 1: Background Material, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 8)
- Carriers' Exhibits No. 2-4, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 9)
- Carriers' Exhibits No. 5-7, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 10)
- Carriers' Exhibits No. 8-10, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 11)
- Memorandum Brief for the Brotherhood of Railroad Switchmen, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 12)
- Mediation Agreement Case No. A-7128, 1965 (Box 1-2, Folder 13)
- Brotherhood Exhibit No. 1, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 14)
- Brotherhood Exhibit No. 2 Photographs, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 15)
- Brotherhood Exhibits No. 3-4, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 16)
- Brotherhood Exhibit No. 5, 1971 (Box 1-2, Folder 17)
- Brotherhood Exhibit No. 5-B Photographs, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood Exhibit No. 5-C Photographs, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood Exhibit No. 5-D Photographs, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood Exhibits No. 6-8, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood Exhibits 9-10, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood Exhibit No. 11, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood Exhibits No. 13-16, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Brotherhood Exhibits No. 18-20, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Apprentice Signalman Training Program Text Book and Exam 1-4, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Apprentice Signalman Training Programs Textbook and Exam 5-8, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Brotherhood Statement, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Agreement with National Railway Labor Conference, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Arbitration Board No. 298, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 179, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)